- +918200494180
- abhigyanfanasia001@gmail.com
- @kabhigyaan
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/abhigyan-fanasia
- HSR Layout, Bengaluru, KA

EDUCATION

BA in Media &
Communication Broadcast Media
Specialization
Manipal Institute of
Communication, MAHE
2020- 2023

EXPERTISE

Adobe Premiere Pro Blender After Effects Photoshop Product Photography Audio Mixing & Mastering FL Studio Ableton Live

LANGUAGES

English Hindi Gujarati

ABHIGYAN F

Photographer/Videographer/Video Editor

ABOUT ME

I am a creative and detail-oriented visual storyteller, with a keen eye for aesthetics, who specializes in combining visuals, audio, and the story together to create content that resonates with the target audience. In my free time, I enjoy taking walks and photographing subjects that capture my interest, and also produce music.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Q August 2023- Present

Vaco Binary Semantics LLP - Full Time

Photographer & Video Editor

- Worked with different clients and captured photos and videos of their products/service as per their requirements
- Gathered and edited raw footages and audio to deliver videos that are brand consistent
- Designed promos and posters for the company and its clients

June 2023 - August 2023 Soapywise - Full Time

Photographer, Videographer & Editor

- Created engaging visual content for the company's website, YouTube channel
- Photographed and shot videos of products capturing the brand essence
- Selected, sourced and set up props for shoots
- Shot, gathered, edited and fine-tuned raw footages and audio

May 2022- July 2022 RAS Media Pvt Ltd - Internship

Photographer & Video/Photo Editor

- Collaborated with art directors to shoot and retouch product photos
- Set up lighting and props for e-commerce company's product catalogue
- Shot and edited videos of models and products